We just launched our new Feastables bar,
which is new branding
and all new formula. It tastes amazing.
I like it.
And to celebrate,
I paid a bunch of people
to make commercials for it, ranging
from $1 all the way up to $10,000.
And we're going to see
if more money equals a better commercial,
starting with this $1 commercial.
Okay.
It's just a person moving it.
They're filming their computer monitor.
This is clearly a joke.
What is that?
Why wouldn't
you just record on your screen?
This is probably their way of saying
screw you for only paying a dollar.
Yeah, I can't imagine anybody
would give you any care for $1.
I mean, to be honest, for television
this is actually a lot of effort.
Oh, it's over.
That was awesome.
No, if I ran that as an ad during
the Super Bowl?
No.
So far you get what you pay for.
That sucked.
Now, let's jump
over to the $50 commercial.
Now it's going to get better.
Well, as long as they don't start
drawing it. What is this?
At least they're not recording
with a phone this time.
There's no music.
What do you want
from these people? $50.
At what price point do we get
sound with our commercial?
It's getting better.
Well, it ended abruptly.
Okay.
Didn't really get to look at it, did we?
Surely
the $100 commercial has audio.
It does.
Matthew, No junk food.
We need to start eating better.
What?
Who made this?
So just follow me and I'll lead you
right to the healthier snacks.
- What is going on?
- This makes me really uncomfortable.
- And I don't know why.
- I love this.
I'm in pain.
Way too many words.
I haven't listened to anything
they've said.
What are you doing in the candy
section?
Looking at candy.
Get to the point.
Just look at these.
Sea salt. Deez nuts.
These aren't even the new ones.
The whole point of the commercial
is our new bars.
You suck.
This is what it looks like now.
Surely the $10,000 commercial
will be better.
Let's see. The $500 one.
Feastables.
Don't mind if I do.
I'm down. I love it.
That was a cool effect.
I like that. Oh, the hand.
This is the best thing that's ever
been created.
That was pretty good.
I mean, imagine
you're flipping on TikTok,
and then you see someone
just go Feastables.
After watching that commercial.
Do you want to eat this amazing
chocolate?
- Yes.
- Well, yes I do.
It’s nice to have a Feastable
I'd love to share a piece with you.
I love jingles.
It’s really the least that I can do.
This is fire.
MrBeast has made a treat for me…
And you.
How did I know?
Oh, it's popping up. Pop off.
He could have made the background
a little cleaner for $500.
I'm sorry.
What is?
Yeah, for him to clean up his room and like
iron the shirt in the background.
That's. That's $1,000.
For $500 I don't want to see
a single Funko Pop in the frame.
Wait, did he add
that in or is that
just a plate with a
Feastable score?
I genuinely can't tell.
You know what? Just because
of that, it's worth the $500.
Thank you, sir.
MrBeast asked us to make
a commercial for Feastables.
The budget was $500.
We made Feastable s'mores instead.
Best decision ever.
We also made this.
Oh, this is really good.
This is the first actual
real commercial so far.
Thanks for the chocolate. Feastables.
You're welcome.
I mean, it had beautiful shots,
but that wasn't really an ad.
That was more of them just saying hi to me.
Let's see how the $750 commercial
turned out.
Beast anime.
Cool.
This is so cool.
That's really cool.
This is awesome.
- All right, I'll say it.
- I was going to say it.
I'll say it. It was a little short.
Well, animation takes a long time.
I agree. It was awesome.
I love the quality.
It made me look way cooler than I do
in real life.
All that just a little short.
That was $750.
I wonder what the $10,000 one
looks like.
- It's so good.
- Yes.
This is really uncomfortable.
I don't think we should put this
on TV.
That's.
This is a commercial.
Nothing makes me want to buy
chocolate like rats eating it.
I can't tell if this is good for our
brand or not, but it's funny.
All right, now,
the thousand dollar commercial.
We're dropping thow-ee's.
The zoom in.
Tareq would nerd out about this.
Tareq is like, "All right,
this is the best one yet."
- Oh, that was sweet.
- I'm sorry, but...
I'm not kissing somebody
just so I can eat chocolate.
They bought a jersey.
High effort.
Oh no. He is out of Feastables.
If you're wondering where you
can buy Feastables, go to Walmart.
Go to Walmart.
$2,000.
Now we're starting
to get to the beefy price point.
- I thought it was chocolate, not beef.
- My bad.
Well, it's a film set.
- That looks cool.
- I like this song.
This is a meta commercial.
The whole point
is shooting a commercial
about shooting a commercial.
I mean, they make the product look good.
There we go.
That's a cool shot.
Oh, it fell. Ha ha. Quirky.
This is still going.
I mean, you paid a lot of money.
I did pay two grand, so.
Why was that funny too?
He just poured milk on it.
Nice.
Oh, that was the ending.
I don't get it.
My head hurts.
Next.
He's got veiny hands.
I understand
why his veins are popping out.
Look how tight his watch is.
Jeez, tight watch.
You're going to cut off circulation.
Needs to clean the nails a little bit.
I'm sorry.
All right, first the veins,
second the nails.
$3,000. He couldn't go get
a manicure first?
I think your nails are fine.
Hey tight watch?
I respect you.
Oh, that's a pretty shot. That was it?
What?
I hope your watch falls off, bro.
Now it's time for the $5,000
commercial.
What's after 5K?
The $10,000 commercial.
Loud equals funny.
If you were me four years ago.
I thought that was not chocolate.
- Are you eating my Feastables?
- No, man, it wasn't me.
I can see it all over your face.
It isn't even feasible that
I feasted on the Feastables.
I've been on the farm all day
fantasizing about those Feastables.
It's an entirely new formula.
It is, brownie points
for mentioning the new formula.
Brownie points for his cheetah
print pants.
Hey guys, where's the dog...?
Told you.
Oh, now he's eating his Feastables.
That is better.
- I don't like.
- I love that.
Find your favorite flavor from milk
chocolate, milky milky, milk crunch.
Milky milky.
Feastables.
They're better than dog...
- Points off for swearing.
- Yes.
More importantly, though,
I want you to comment down below.
Did that make you want to go buy
chocolate from Walmart?
That's the best one yet.
Now we have a second
$5000 commercial.
We sent everyone
a bunch of our new bars
and on top of that,
if they requested me to film footage,
I filmed it and sent it to them.
This is the first one
to ask me to film something.
Let's see how they use it.
This is so cool.
Well, it's got a dog.
I'm already on board.
Tell me that my bad vibes
are hitting the streets.
What is going on?
This is going to change the world.
Some point, we'll see
the Feastables chocolate, I assume.
Or not.
Maybe they just...
- Okay, there we go.
- Yeah!
We finally see the product.
Deliver these
and make them smile.
Hey!
Oh no.
What's in the briefcase, Happy Feet?
I'm going to be saying
that for the rest of my life.
Look, they're doing good deeds now
because they're MrBeast.
The world will never be happy.
Bro, what in the?
Did this guy think we wanted a movie?
Because I told them
I wanted a commercial.
That was a good shot.
Delivered to the world.
- That was you.
- That was me.
They asked me to film that clip.
They literally went out of their way to
ask you for a one-second clip of you?
And you put in 1% effort into it.
"Feast like a beast.
Feastables.com."
That was really a lot of effort.
And now the moment you've all been
waiting for.
I know I have.
Let's see what a $10,000 commercial is.
Better be good.
Halloween.
I got some Trick or Treaters.
Trick or Treat.
They took the whole thing.
This guy looks like he'd steal
some chocolate.
The product looks
very good in that shot.
Oh no.
Bisexual lighting.
This is shot so well.
It's a pirate.
Oh gosh.
Are they going to steal more candy?
Trick or Treat? I'm a banana.
He just can't get enough, can he?
Wait, watch. He's going to re-ring it.
He's going to have
a different costume on.
Oh, I knew it.
Twick or Tweat.
That was really uncomfortably gross.
Man, didn't I tell you to get...
Trick or Treat.
Happy Halloween, fellas.
Yeah, that cowboy just looks like
people I went to high school with.
That's him.
That's the guy who stole my candy.
I'm down for this.
I like this.
Feastables.
World's best chocolate.
I mean...
I...
To be fair, I gave them chocolate bars
with no direction.
I don't know if this would
convert to sales, but they're funny.
So if these commercials made you
want to try Feastables,
go to Walmart and
try our milk chocolate bar,
our milk crunch bar, our almond bar,
our peanut butter bar,
our dark chocolate bar,
our dark chocolate sea salt bar
or our peanut butter crunch bar.
All seven flavors
are now available at Walmart.
Go give it a try
and tell me what you think.
Do it or I won't like you.
We'll punch you.
Whatever we're ending the video.